Changyeon Kim

Naver 1784, 95 Jeongjail-ro, Bundang-gu, Seongnam-si, Gyeonggi-do 13561, South Korea

□ (+82) 10-9020-3925 | 🗷 changyeon.kim@kaist.ac.kr | 🏕 changyeon.page | 🖸 csmile-1006 | 🞓 Changyeon.Kim

Research Interest

My research goal is to make RL algorithms that can be well adapted to the real world. To this end, I am focusing on designing RL algorithms to tackle practical and challenging scenarios, e.g., unseen novel environments and environments without well-shaped rewards. I am also broadly interested in areas related to RL, including RL leveraging pre-trained representation learning, language-conditioned RL, and offline RL.

Education

Advisor: Jinwoo Shin

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology

Mar. 2022 - Present

PHD IN ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE

Daejeon, S.Korea

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology

B.Sc. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND MATHEMATICS (MINOR)

Daejeon, S.Korea

Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2021

Publications

C: Conference, W: Workshop, P: Preprint, *: Equal contribution

[W2] Guide Your Agent with Adaptive Multimodal Rewards

Hawaii, USA

CHANGYEON KIM, YOUNGGYO SEO, HAO LIU, LISA LEE, JINWOO SHIN, HONGLAK LEE, KIMIN LEE

July, 2023.

International Conference on Machine Learning Workshop on New Frontiers in Learning, Control, and Dynamical Systems (ICMLW), 2023.

[C2] Preference Transformer: Modeling Human Preferences using Transformers for RL

Kigali, Rwanda

CHANGYEON KIM*, JONGJIN PARK*, JINWOO SHIN, HONGLAK LEE, PIETER ABBEEL, KIMIN LEE

May, 2023.

• International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR), 2023.

[W1] Dynamics-Augmented Decision Transformer for Offline Dynamics Generalization

New Orleans, LA, USA

Changyeon Kim*, Junsu Kim*, Younggyo Seo, Kimin Lee, Honglak Lee, Jinwoo Shin

Nov, 2022.

• Neural Information Processing Systems Workshop on Offline Reinforcement Learning (NeurIPSW), 2022.

[C1] Collecting the Public Perception of AI and Robot Rights

Online

GABRIEL LIMA, CHANGYEON KIM, SEUNGHO RYU, CHIHYOUNG JEON, MEEYOUNG CHA

Oct. 2020.

Conference on Computer-Supported Cooperative Work and Social Computing (CSCW), 2020.

[P1] MOI-Mixer: Improving MLP-Mixer with Multi Order Interactions in Sequential Recommendation

HOJOON LEE, DONGYOON HWANG, SUNGHWAN HONG, CHANGYEON KIM, SEUNGRYONG KIM, JAEGUL CHOO

· ArXiv Preprint.

Work Experience _____

External Collaborator Remote

LISA LEE (GOOGLE RESEARCH) Apr. 2023 - present

• Developed an imitation learning algorithm [W2] using multimodal representations for improving generalization ability in unseen variations.

External Collaborator Remote

KIMIN LEE (GOOGLE RESEARCH), HONGLAK LEE (UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN)

Mar. 2022 - present

- Developed an imitation learning algorithm [W2] using multimodal representations for improving generalization ability in unseen variations.
- Developed a reinforcement learning algorithm [W1] for improving generalization ability in varying dynamics.
- Developed a preference-based reinforcement learning algorithm [C2] for modeling non-Markovian human preferences.

CHANGYEON KIM · RÉSUMÉ JUNE 20, 2023

Machine Learning Engineer

KAKAO, RECOMMENDATION TEAM

Seongnam, S.Korea
Dec. 2020 - Feb. 2022

• Developed ML platform for recommendation system.

- Developed Python backend for a web application providing data analysis and visualization of Kakao data.
- Implemented data pipeline from user feedback to refined user-item interaction matrix data.
- Deployed DropoutNet for providing qualitative recommendations to cold-start users.

Research InternSeongnam, S.Korea

KAKAO, RECOMMENDATION TEAM

Jun. 2020 - Aug. 2020

- · Developed an advanced similar recommendation model for Piccoma (cartoon platform of Kakao Japan).
- Conducted research on relationships between offline/online evaluation on the recommendation system.

Research Intern Daejeon, S. Korea

DATA SCIENCE GROUP, INSTITUTE OF BASIC SCIENCE

Jul. 2019 - Nov. 2020

- · Conducted research on how much human rights can be granted to robots using AMT (Amazon Mechanical Turk) [C1].
- Implemented BiLSTM model for extracting game higlight by game log.
- Conducted research identifying the "Pilgrimage" articles and analyzing its pattern in Naver News corpora.

Research Interen Seoul, S.Korea

NETMARBLE

Jun. 2018 - Aug. 2018

- Implemented algorithm for detecting "fraud" account in online-game
- Analyzed repetitive group reaction from time-series data of game activities.

Honors & Awards

2023	Travel Award , International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR)	Kigali, Rwanda
2019	Dean's List (Fall Semester), Department of Engineering, KAIST	Daejeon, S.Korea
2019	Line Scholarship (Fall Semester), School of Computing, KAIST	Daejeon, S.Korea
2017 - 19	National Science and Engineering Scholarship, Korea Ministry of Science and ICT	Daejeon, S.Korea
2017	Kwanjeong Scholarship (Spring Semester), KAIST	Daejeon, S.Korea

Academic Services _____

Workshop Reviewer ICML Workshop on New Frontiers in Learning, Control, and Dynamical Systems (Frontiers4LCD) 2023

Skills

ML/DL Pytorch, Pytorch-lightning, JAX/Flax

Programming Python, C++

Big Data Kafka, SQL, MongoDB, Hadoop, Trino(Presto)

DevOps Git, Docker, Kubernetes

Languages Korean (Native), English (Fluent), Japanese (Advanced)

JUNE 20, 2023 CHANGYEON KIM · RÉSUMÉ